<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>Arcadia Page | Writer | Artist ❤️</title>
    
    
    <description>Writer and Comic Artist</description>
    
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>7 Simple Organization Tips for INFPs</title>
        <description>
          
          There are a ton of books and blogs out there on being organized. As someone who struggles with organization, my thoughts always go to, &quot;Is this organizational tip easy? Does it work with how I think?&quot;Since writing my book, Idealist Dreams: How I Learned to Plan as an INFP, I...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 07:18:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020/05/7-simple-organization-tips-for-infps.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020/05/7-simple-organization-tips-for-infps.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dear INFP Writer, It's Okay to Have Too Many Ideas</title>
        <description>
          
          In the function stack of INFPs, extroverted intuition is the second in command. It is your inspiration and idea machine. Extroverted intuition (Ne) enjoys combining ideas and feeling inspired. It's all about being curious, finding new ideas from the external world, and connecting those ideas together in unique ways. Since...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 05:49:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020/04/dear-infp-writer-its-okay-to-have-too.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020/04/dear-infp-writer-its-okay-to-have-too.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>10 Tips on Working With Your Strengths as an INFP Writer</title>
        <description>
          
          Writing allows us to express ourselves and sort through our inner world. Fi Ne Si TeIn the function stack of the INFP, introverted feeling is at the top. It's the function INFPs are the most comfortable using. And introverted feeling, with its deep interest in the personal lives of others,...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 07:18:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020/04/10-tips-on-working-with-your-strengths.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020/04/10-tips-on-working-with-your-strengths.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Digital Detox Project: How to Have Mindful App Usage</title>
        <description>
          
          I am an app addict. I don't know how many apps I've installed and uninstalled just to find the right thing that fits my needs. I think a lot of good comes from trying to find digital services that fit the way you work and create. If it takes experimenting...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/the-digital-detox-project-how-to-have.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020/03/the-digital-detox-project-how-to-have.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Digital Detox Project: Reducing Email Anxiety</title>
        <description>
          
          Like many people in this modern life, I've struggled for a long time with email. I'm tired of being stressed out over email. Over the past week or so, I've taken some decisive steps to take control of my inbox.Just to give some background on my personal mission at this...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020/02/the-digital-detox-project-reducing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020/02/the-digital-detox-project-reducing.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finding my Blend as a Multi-passionate Blogger</title>
        <description>
          
          My first blog was Manga &amp;amp; Mascara. The purpose of that blog was to write about my process of creating comics. It was perfect at the time because I was actively working on a webcomic. But when I posted the last page of my comic and all was done, I...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 06:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020/01/finding-my-blend-as-multi-passionate.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020/01/finding-my-blend-as-multi-passionate.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Combine Digital Notes with Analog Notes</title>
        <description>
          
          I am always on a quest to connect the pen and paper tools I love to my digital life. Unlike with apps, paper never holds me back when it comes to expression. I can write, draw, and even collage on it with little effort.Yet, I do much of my work...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 07:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/12/how-to-combine-digital-notes-with.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/12/how-to-combine-digital-notes-with.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exploring Multipotential with a 30 Day Etsy Challenge</title>
        <description>
          
          For a long time, my Etsy shop has been sitting around doing not much of anything. Recently, I've decided to use my Etsy shop to stretch my multipotentialite muscles. Not only would it be fun, but I could also learn something about my creative process across different disciplines.My 30 Day...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 08:03:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/11/exploring-multipotential-with-30-day.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/11/exploring-multipotential-with-30-day.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Too Busy to Write? Here are 4 Flexible Writing Schedules to Try</title>
        <description>
          
          Having the desire to write but feeling like you don't have the time is a motivation killer. That project you want to finish weighs on your mind. The longer it sits there, the more you feel like getting around to it is impossible.&amp;nbsp;I've finished projects even when facing time and...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 06:30:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/11/too-busy-to-write-here-are-4-flexible.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/11/too-busy-to-write-here-are-4-flexible.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Recommended Reading for INFP Writers</title>
        <description>
          
          For a long time, I refused to read books about the craft of writing. I used to think, &quot;Why should I read about writing when I could be writing?&quot; For a long time, I felt reading fiction and comics was the best way to learn how to write. How-to-Write books...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 06:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/10/recommended-reading-for-infp-writers.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/10/recommended-reading-for-infp-writers.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thoughts on How I Work as an INFP Writer</title>
        <description>
          
          When I started writing this post, the first question I had was, &quot;Is this a guide?&quot; In some ways it is. But in many ways, it's not.INFP writers need something better than a guide. They need permission. Um, let me rephrase that: We need permission. We need permission to be...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 06:58:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/10/thoughts-on-how-i-work-as-infp-writer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/10/thoughts-on-how-i-work-as-infp-writer.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How I Make Use of My Random Writing Ideas as an INFP Writer</title>
        <description>
          
          For me writing a story rarely sticks to the plan. Settings, plots, and characters that I believe are the perfect fit can be out of style a few chapters in. However, instead of getting frustrated by this, I look forward to it, because I know this is another way that...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 05:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/10/how-i-make-use-of-my-random-writing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/10/how-i-make-use-of-my-random-writing.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>4 Unforgettable Lessons I Learned from my 1st Writing Retreat</title>
        <description>
          
          Sometimes while working on a fiction project, you can hit a point where you lose sight of your story. You can miss that excitement you had when you first started it, or something about the story doesn't feel right anymore.As an INFP, ideas often come to me non-chronologically, and that...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 05:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/09/4-unforgettable-lessons-i-learned-from.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/09/4-unforgettable-lessons-i-learned-from.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How You Can Easily Create an Immersive Story Setting on One Page</title>
        <description>
          
          Currently, I'm working on a story with a cyberpunk inspired setting. As I work on it, I am even more amazed at how developing a setting is just important as developing good characters. Setting impacts not only what characters do and experience in a story, but also what the reader...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 07:12:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/09/how-you-can-easily-create-immersive.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/09/how-you-can-easily-create-immersive.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Build a Productive Writing Routine</title>
        <description>
          
          Sometimes it can be hard to find a writing schedule that works, especially when you have a busy life.But the nice thing about writing is that it doesn't take much time to write a few words, and thanks to mobile devices, it's possible to write anywhere at anytime.Here are two...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 05:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/09/how-to-build-productive-writing-routine.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/09/how-to-build-productive-writing-routine.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Live a Life of Small Adventures</title>
        <description>
          
          The idea of small adventures has been a large part of my life since childhood. However, I didn't notice that this concept was meaningful until various people have recently pointed it out to me.It will take a lot of writing to fully express what it means to live a life...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 05:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/08/how-to-live-life-of-small-adventures.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/08/how-to-live-life-of-small-adventures.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Using Journaling to Transform How You Plan for the Day</title>
        <description>
          
          I've always believed in the power of journaling. Journaling has helped me to see more clearly in my daily life, visualize the goals I want to reach, and express my feelings. Lately I came across an interesting planning technique from Cal Newport featured by MakeUseOf.com. Then I also read this...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 05:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/07/using-journaling-to-transform-how-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/07/using-journaling-to-transform-how-you.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Being Highly Sensitive and Consistently Creative</title>
        <description>
          
          Lately I've been gaining new appreciation for how important it is to have a good pace and routine when working on creative projects.Every day I've been editing a little bit of&amp;nbsp; How I Learned to Plan as an INFP. Using the GoodTime app for Android, I work on my book...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 05:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/06/being-highly-sensitive-and-consistently.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/06/being-highly-sensitive-and-consistently.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Simplicity is the Reduction of Choice</title>
        <description>
          
          So far I've written two new chapters for my book, How I Learned to Plan as an INFP. I'm halfway done with the overall updating process. I'm excited about including new things and simpler methods.First, when I started writing this book, I was using about four different programs: Focus Writer,...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 06:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/05/simplicity-is-reduction-of-choice.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/05/simplicity-is-reduction-of-choice.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Hidden Skill INFPs Have for Saving Money </title>
        <description>
          
          The inside of the fridge is looking bare. There is a flimsy, half paper carton of eggs, a gallon of milk, dark purple grapes that are getting riper by the day, a thawing bag of beef chili, and a dark green spring leaf salad. Although it may not look like...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 06:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/04/the-hidden-skill-infps-have-for-saving.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/04/the-hidden-skill-infps-have-for-saving.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
